The Hunt Has Begun...
Vampire Journals is a horror, fantasy, thriller film directed by Ted Nicolaou.
A 19th century vampire stalks a more powerful vampire lord in his
quest to gain revenge over the death of his mistress.
In his search for the vampire lord in Eastern Europe he kills many of his servants
and fellow vampires while cursing another to vampirism as well.
Ash, played by Jonathon Morris.
Zachary, played by David Gunn.
Sofia, played by Kirsten Cerre.
Iris, played by Starr Andreeff.
Cassandra, played by Ilinca Goia.
Vampire, played by Constantin Bărbulescu.
Interview with the Vampire is a 1994 American gothic horror film directed by Neil Jordan and written by
Anne Rice, based on her 1976 novel of the same name, and starring Tom Cruise and Brad Pitt.
It focuses on Lestat (Cruise) and Louis (Pitt), beginning with
Louis' transformation into a vampire by Lestat in 1791.
The film chronicles their time together, and their turning of
young Claudia (Kirsten Dunst) into a vampire.
The narrative is framed by a modern-day interview, in which Louis tells
his story to a San Francisco reporter (Christian Slater).
The supporting cast features Antonio Banderas and Stephen Rea.
The film was released by Warner Bros.
on November 11, 1994 to generally positive reviews and was a commercial
success, grossing $223.7 million against a $60 million budget.
It received two Academy Award nominations for Best
Art Direction and Best Original Score.
Kirsten Dunst was additionally nominated for a Golden Globe for
Best Supporting Actress for her role in the film.
A stand-alone sequel, Queen of the Damned, was released in 2002, with Stuart
Townsend and Matthew Newton replacing Cruise and Banderas respectively.
The film explores themes of sword, vampire, impalement, severed, severed head.
The tone is dark and intense.